One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Roger's Adventure
Roger'ın Macerası
Ouch!
Oof!
So cold!
Çok soğuk!
With the help of Gan Fall, the god above the clouds, we reached the sea safely.
Bulutların üzerindeki Tanrı Gan Fall sayesinde denize sağ salim vardık.
The North Pole!
Kuzey Kutbu!
No, the South Pole!
Güney Kutbu!
You won't budge, huh?!
Pes etmeyeceksin, ha?!
You got it! And I'll keep sayin' it cause I'm right!
Aynen! Haklıyım ve vazgeçmeyeceğim!
Knock it off!
Kesin şunu!
All you two ever do is fight!
Tek yaptığınız kavga etmek!
Our destination is none other than the final island on the Grand Line!
Hedefimiz, Grand Line'ın son adası!
But to get there, we need copies of all four lode poneglyphs.
Ama oraya ulaşmak için dört yol poneglifinin kopyası şart!
Like that stone we found on the sky island?
Gökyüzü adasındaki o taş gibi mi?
There is one in Wano.
Wano'da bir tane var.
Mrowr Mokomo Dukedom has one, too.
Mokomo Dükalığı'nde de bir tane var-miyav.
Your homelands both have stones like that?!
Ülkenizde böyle taşlar var mıydı?
Unlike the one on the sky island...
Gökyüzü adasındakinin aksine,
– ...it's red!
– ...kırmızı renkte!
Those are the ones I want the most!
Tam aradığım tipte taş!
Why didn't you say something?!
Niye daha önce söylemediniz be?!
So we'll have two out of four!
Yani dört taneden ikisi elimizde gibi!
No, we also snatched a copy of Linlin's lode poneglyph.
Evet, ayrıca Linlin'in yol poneglifinin de bir kopyasını aldık.
And I've got a hunch where the last one is.
Galiba sonuncusunun da nerede olduğunu biliyorum.
Nice going, Roger!
Harika, Roger!
Yeah, I can't believe our luck!
Evet, amma şanslıyız ha!
We'll really have all four!
Gerçekten dördüne de sahip olacağız!
Sorry to spoil the celebration, but something's wrong with the ship.
Eğlencenizi böldüğüm için özür dilerim ama gemide bir sorun var.
What?
Ne?
I'm no shipwright, so I can't tell what's busted.
Gemi marangozu olmadığım için sorunun kaynağını bilemiyorum.
Well then, I know just the place!
O hâlde, ihtiyacımız olan yeri biliyorum!
Where?
Neresi?
The City of Water, Water Seven!
Su Şehri, Water Seven!
The City of Water?
Su Şehri mi?
Sounds romantic!
Kulağa romantik geliyor!
Alright men, let's go!
Pekâlâ beyler, gidelim!
– Yeah!
– Evet!
Thus, we headed to the shipbuilding town for repairs.
Böylece onarım için gemi yapım şehrine doğru yola çıktık.
Scrap Island Water Seven
Water Seven, Hurda Adası
Tom (The Shipwright Who Built Roger's Ship)
Tom (Roger'ın gemisini yapan gemi marangozu)
It's damn good to see you, Roger!
Seni görmek harika, Roger!
Tom!
Tom!
– Tom!
– Tom!
Hey, Mr. Tom!
Tom-san!
It's been a while, guys!
Uzun zaman oldu, beyler!
Yeah, I missed you!
Evet, seni özledim!
You finish that train yet?
Meşhur trenini tamamladın mı?
You mean the sea train?!
Deniz treninden mi bahsediyorsun?!
No way! It's still in the design phase!
Saçmalama! Hâlâ tasarım aşamasında!
Kokoro A Beautiful Secretary Tom's Workers
Tom'un Çalışanları'nın Güzel Sekreteri Kokoro
You guys are as noisy as ever!
Yine her zamanki gibi gürültücüsünüz!
Are you an orphan?!
Sen yetim misin?!
Do you want me to introduce you to our captain?
Seni kaptanımızla tanıştırmamı ister misin?
You guys are pirates, right?
Siz korsansınız, değil mi?
What of it?
Ne olmuş?
Then, no way.
Asla olmaz.
I just got ditched by pirates.
Korsanlar tarafından yeni terk edildim.
Ditched?!
Terk mi edildin?!
Bad timing!
Kötü zamanlama!
♪ Gather up all of the crew! ♪ ♪ Time to ship out Binks' brew! ♪
♪ Binks'in sakesini ulaştırmaya gidelim ♪
♪ Pirates, we tirelessly ♪ ♪ are challenging the sea! ♪
♪ Bize derler korsan, aşarız tüm denizleri ♪
♪ Somewhere in the endless sky, ♪ ♪ stormy winds are blowing by! ♪
♪ Fırtına bulutları, sardı yine gökleri ♪
♪ Waves are dancing, evening comes, ♪ ♪ it's time to sound the drums! ♪
♪ Dalgalar dans eder, vurun davula çalsın müzikler! ♪
♪ Steady men, and never fear, ♪ ♪ future skies are always clear! ♪
♪ Korku rüzgârına kapılıp da umutsuzluğa düşme ♪
Tequila Wolf A Country on a Bridge
Köprü Ülkesi, Tequila Wolf
♪ Pound your feet, clap your hands ♪ ♪ till sunny days return! ♪
♪ Yarın güneş, yeniden doğacak elbette ♪
Sabaody Archipelago
Sabaody Takımadaları
Let's set sail!
Dalalım!
Fishman Island, huh?
Balıkadam Adası, ha?
I went there once with Whitekichi!
Beyazcık-chan'la gitmiştik oraya.
Don't drop your guard!
Gardınızı indirmeyin!
No matter how many times you go, your chances of dying won't change!
Kaç kez giderseniz gidin, her seferinde ölme şansınız vardır!
Rayleigh! Did you hear that?
Rayleigh! Duydun mu?
What are you talking about?
Neden bahsediyorsun?
There's nothing to hear this deep.
Bu diplikte hiçbir ses duyulmaz.
No, I can hear it, too.
Ben de duydum gibi.
You, too, Oden?
Sen de mi, Oden?
Who's talking this deep in the water?!
Denizin bu kadar dibinde kim ötüyor lan?!
Toki! That's Fishman Island!
Toki! Burası Balıkadam Adası!
How curious...
Çok ilginç...
It seems like the whole island is in a bubble...
Sanki bütün ada bir baloncuğun içinde.
Those are...
Bunlar...
...fishmen!
Balık adamlar!
They have surrounded us!
Etrafımızı sardılar!
State your business, surface dwellers!
Yüzeyde yaşayanlar, geliş sebebinizi belirtin!
Whoa, wait, wait. Look closer!
Dur, bekle. İyi bak!
It's me! Roger!
Benim, Roger!
Great Knight Neptune!
Yüce Şövalye Neptune!
Roger?
Roger?
Oh, it all makes sense!
Ah, şimdi anlıyorum!
So you guys are gonna do it!
Yani bunu gerçekten yapacaksınız!
Mermaid Cove Ryugu Kingdom
Ryugu Krallığı, Deniz Kızı Koyu
We're not up to any trouble!
Sorun çıkarmak gibi bir niyetimiz yok.
Come on, why are you scared of a prophecy?
Kehanet mi korkuttu seni?
You're better than that!
Sana yakışıyor mu hiç?
It foretold someone breaking the gates of Fishman Island soon!
Yakında biri gelip Balıkadam Adası'nın kapılarını yıkacakmış.
And now that you've arrived, it all points to...
Sen de gelince, taşlar yerine oturmaya başladı...
King Neptune, it's been broken!
Neptune-sama, kırdılar!
The sea kings chewed up the gate!
Deniz kralları dış yapıyı kırdılar!
What?! But they're such gentle creatures!
Nasıl olur?! O yaratıklar çok uysaldır!
It can't be true!
Bu doğru olamaz!
It came true...
Gerçekleşti...
The outer bubble's been breached!
Dış baloncuğu patlattılar!
Seal it immediately! Begin emergency repairs!
Derhal el atın! Acil onarımlara başlayın!
We couldn't prevent it.
Bunu önleyemedik.
See?! It wasn't us!
Gördün mü?! Biz değildik!
The sea kings are growing restless because they're waiting for the Mermaid Princess to be born. Sharley Prophet Girl (Three Years Old)
Deniz Kızı Prensesi'nin doğuşunu bekleyen deniz kralları huzursuzlanıyor.
The Mermaid Princess?! That's another prophecy.
Deniz Kızı Prensesi mi? Bir başka kehanet daha...
So the king will have a baby?!
Demek kralın bebeği olacak!
We have to celebrate!
Bunu kutlamalıyız!
Wait, wait!
Bekleyin!
I'm not even married yet!
Henüz evlenmedim bile-jamon!
I've only been king for a few months!
Sadece bir kaç aydır kralım-jamon!
But King Neptune!
Ama Neptune-sama!
She even divined the day that the former king would die!
Eski kralın öleceği günü bile tahmin etmişti!
She also predicted that seductive...
Ayrıca şu seksi...
I mean, seditious mermaid Otohime's political demonstration the other day!
pardon, kışkırtıcı Deniz Kızı Otohime'nin geçen günkü mitingini de bildi!
I-It's not like it brought me any comfort!
B-Bu hiç içimi rahatlatmadı!
Deepwater Grove Ryugu Kingdom
Ryugu Krallığı, Su Altı Ormanı
These days, the whole country is swayed by that girl's prophecies...
Bugünlerde bütün ülke, o kızın kehanetleriyle sarsılıyor...
We didn't come to hear your life story, Neptune.
Hayatını dinlemeye gelmedik, Neptune.
Ah, that's right.
Ah, doğru.
Any luck, Oden?
Nasıl gidiyor, Oden?
Well...
Şey...
There are two, so I thought we could get a lot of information,
İki tane olunca epey bilgi çıkarırız demiştim...
but one of them seems mostly irrelevant.
ama biri konuyla alakasız gibi.
It is a letter of apology from someone named Joyboy.
Joyboy diye bir herifin yazdığı bir özür mektubu bu!
Unbelievable! He really can read the script!
İnanılmaz! Gerçekten yazıtları okuyabiliyor!
More importantly, do you have a weapon capable of controlling sea kings?
Boş ver onu da, deniz krallarını yöneten bir silahınız var mı?
A weapon?!
Bir silah mı?!
The stone on the sky island said it's here.
Gökyüzü adasındaki taşta burada olduğu yazıyordu.
An ancient weapon bearing the name of a god...
Adını bir tanrıdan alan o antik silah...
"Poseidon."
"Poseidon."
To tell you the truth...
Gerçek şu ki...
I felt a slight chill when I heard Sharley's prophecy earlier.
öncesinde Sharley'in kehanetini duyduğumda hafif bir ürperti hissettim.
Once every few centuries in this country,
Bu ülkede neredeyse her yüzyılda bir...
a mermaid who can talk to the sea kings is born.
deniz krallarıyla konuşabilen bir deniz kızı doğar.
Could that mermaid really be...
O deniz kızlarından biri benim...
So your daughter will become the weapon that destroys the world someday?
Yani dünyayı yok edebilecek o silahın kızın olduğunu mu söylüyorsun?
It's just a prophecy!
Bu sadece bir kehanet-jamon!
And even if it's called an ancient weapon, it doesn't have to be used as one!
Adı antik silah diye illa silah olarak kullanılması gerekmez.
I never would've guessed that Poseidon was a mermaid!
Poseidon'un bir deniz kızı olacağı hiç aklıma gelmemişti.
Hey, Sharley, when will the Mermaid Princess be born?
Söyle bakalım Sharley, şu prenses ne zaman doğacak?
Ten!
10 yıl içinde!
Huh?
Ha?
So ten years from now...
Demek 10 yıl içinde...
But, Roger, I can't believe you're interested in such a weapon!
Ama Roger, böyle bir silaha ilgi duyman şaşırttı beni!
I misjudged you!
Seni yanlış tanımışım!
Actually, Neptune, we're after the vast treasure left behind by the people who called it a weapon!
Bak Neptune, biz ona silah diyenlerin geride bıraktığı o koca hazinenin peşindeyiz!
Feel better?
Rahatladın mı?
We won't be coming back to kidnap your hairy daughter!
Bir gün kıllı kızını kaçırmak için gelmeyiz buralara.
She won't be hairy!
Kıllı olmayacak!
♪ Gather up all of the crew! ♪ ♪ Time to ship out Binks' brew! ♪
♪ Binks'in sakesini ulaştırmaya gidelim ♪
♪ Wave goodbye, don't you cry, ♪ ♪ our memories remain. ♪
♪ Günlerimiz geçiyor tıpkı rüya gibi ♪
♪ Days are but a passing dream, ♪ ♪ everlasting though they seem. ♪
♪ Elveda diyen seni bir daha görmesem de...
♪ Beneath the moon we'll meet again, ♪ ♪ the wind's our lullaby! ♪
olan olur üzülme, yarınlar seninle ♪
In the Seas Near Wano
Wano Açıklarında
Hey, Oden!
Oden-san!
What is wrong, Redtaro?
Sorun ne, Kızıl-taro?
Toki collapsed!
Toki-san bayıldı!
What?!
Ne?!
Toki!
Toki!
Do not worry!
Endişelenme!
I am here with you!
Seninleyim!
Oden...
Oden...
Toki has been following you and traveling the world,
Toki seni takip edip dünyayı dolaşıyor,
but her original destination was Wano.
ama onun daimi hedefi, Wano.
As Wano draws nearer, she's started to wear down,
Wano'ya yaklaştıkça yıpranmaya başladı...
and the fatigue of the long journey has hit her.
ve uzun yolculuğunun yorgunluğu onu vurdu.
If she continues, she could die.
Yolculuğa devam ederse ölebilir.
She should disembark at Wano and bring her journey to a close.
Wano'da inip yolculuğunu sonlandırmalı.
Kin'emon and the others don't know Lady Toki well.
Kin'emon ve diğerleri Toki-sama'yı pek tanımıyorlar.
So Inuarashi and I will accompany her.
Bu yüzden Inuarashi'yle birlikte ona eşlik edeceğiz.
The place is unfamiliar to them, so I'm sure they'll feel lonely.
Orası onlara yabancı, eminim yalnızlık çekeceklerdir.
Leave Lady Toki in our care.
Toki-sama'yı bize bırakın.
There is no way that I will just–
Hayatta olmaz–
Toki?
Toki?
You have to go, Oden!
Gitmelisin, Oden-san!
What are you saying?!
Ne diyorsun?!
If you quit over a little thing like this...
Böyle ufak bir mesele yüzünden pes edersen...
I...
inan...
will dissolve our marriage!
evliliğimizi sonlandırırım!
We have eagerly awaited the day you would return, Lord Oden!
Geri döneceğiniz günü sabırsızlıkla bekledik, Oden-sama!
We have endeavored to look after Kuri in your absence, however...
Sizin yokluğunuzda Kuri'ye bakmaya çalıştık ama...
Not just Kuri, but all of Wano is–
Gerçi sadece Kuri değil, tüm Wano'ya–
Wait!
Bekleyin!
– Huh?
– Ha?
If you truly care about Oden...
Oden'i cidden önemsiyorsanız...
Please!
lütfen...
Let him go!
bırakın gitsin!
I...
Ben...
I will be away for a little longer.
Biraz daha buralardan uzak olacağım.
Even as I turned away, I could tell that something about Wano had changed.
Yüzümü çevirmiş olsam da Wano'da bir şeylerin değiştiğini görebiliyordum.
I knew that should I look back, I would never resume my voyage.
Geriye dönüp bakarsam yolculuğuma asla devam edemeyeceğimi biliyordum.
– Damn you, Lord Oden!
– Hay sizin, Oden-sama!
– You deadbeat!
– Pislik herif!
I quickly made a rubbing of the poneglyph in Wano and returned to the sea.
Hızlıca Wano'daki poneglifi inceledim ve denize geri döndüm.
It was my first time home in four years, but I only stayed for a few hours.
Dört yılın ardından ilk kez evime ayak bastım ama sadece birkaç saat kaldım.
You deadbeat.
Harbiden pisliksin he...
How about reading the script yourself then?!
O hâlde yazıtları kendin okumaya ne dersin?
I'm truly sorry, Oden.
Gerçekten çok üzgünüm, Oden.
Next, we headed to the Mokomo Dukedom, Nekomamushi and Inuarashi's homeland.
Ardından Nekomamushi ve Inuarashi'nin yurdu olan Mokomo Dükalığı'na doğru yola çıktık.
It was said to be on the back of an elephant.
Koca bir filin sırtındaymış meğer!
I was told that we could only get to Zou with this vivre card.
Zou'ya ancak bu vivre kartla ulaşabileceğimiz söylendi.
You are indeed correct that this is no island!
Haklıymışsın! Cidden ada değilmiş!
An elephant?!
Fil miymiş?!
Whose voice is this?
Kimin sesi bu?
Oden, what's the matter?
Oden-san, sorun nedir?
Well, I suppose it is nothing, but I have this peculiar feeling...
Şey, önemli değil ama içimde tuhaf bir his var...
Mokomo Dukedom
Mokomo Dükalığı
Duke Genghis Baan
Mokomo Dükalığı Dükü
A letter from Inuarashi and Nekomamushi!
Inuarashi ve Nekomamushi'den bir mektup!
So they're still alive!
Demek hayattalar...
Those rapscallions...!
bizim şu haylazlar.
Their disappearance caused quite the commotion!
Kaybolmaları büyük bir kargaşaya neden olmuştu!
Thank you for putting our minds at ease.
İçimizi rahatlattığınız için teşekkürler.
I feel uneasy...
Kendimi huzursuz hissediyorum.
Are you okay, Oden? That doesn't sound like you.
İyi misin, Oden? Pek kendinde değilsin gibi.
I know how you feel, Oden.
Nasıl hissettiğini anlıyorum, Oden.
You, too, Captain Roger?!
Siz de mi, Kaptan Roger?!
It kind of feels like I'm being watched by something really big...
Sanki çok büyük bir şey tarafından izleniyormuşum gibi...
Here it is!
İşte burada!
The last lode poneglyph!
Son yol poneglifini de bulduk!
The Kozuki family crest!
Kozuki Hanesi'nin simgesi!
So we truly share a brotherly bond with the minks!
Demek Minklerle aramızda sahiden bir kardeşlik bağı varmış.
I'm beggin' you, take me along!
Beni de yanınıza alın!
Kid, you still have to wait.
Çocuk, daha vaktin gelmedi.
Listen!
Dinle bak.
Everyone gets their own turn.
Herkesin bi' vakti vardır.
My own turn?!
Benim de mi?!
When the time comes, I'm counting on you.
Vaktin gelince bana yardım et!
Okay!
Tamamdır!
I'll help you for sure!
Kesinlikle edeceğim!
Goodbye, Pedro.
Hoşça kal, Pedro.
We found the four lode poneglyphs and several parts of the Rio Poneglyph.
Dört yol poneglifine ek olarak, bir kaç Rio Poneglifi de edindik.
Our adventure's conclusion is approaching.
Maceramızın sonu yaklaşıyor.
In a Port Town
Bir Limanda
Captain, are you okay?!
Kaptan, iyi misin?!
Have you figured out where the final island is?
Son adanın nerede olduğunu bulabildiniz mi?
Yes, we have.
Evet, bulduk.
When should we leave?
Ne zaman yola çıkalım?
Immediately!
Hemen!
– Okay!
– Tamam!
Alright, let's go!
Pekâlâ, hadi gidelim!
For better or for worse, the apprentice Buggyjiro suddenly took ill with a fever
İyi mi kötü mü bilinmez ama miço Buggy-jiro bir anda hastalanıp ateşlendi...
and had to withdraw from the final voyage.
ve son adaya doğru yapacağımız yolculuğa gelemedi.
Only a damn kid would catch a cold right before a great adventure.
Koca maceranın eşiğinde ancak salak bir velet şifayı kapar.
Shut up! I said I'm better now!
Kapa' çeneni! İyileştim diyorum işte!
Your face is red, and you're burning up. Give it a rest.
Yüzün kıpkırmızı ve ateşin var. Biraz rahatlasana artık.
Who'd you say has a big, red nose?!
Kime koca kırmızı burunlu diyorsun lan sen?!
Clean out your ears!
Öyle bir şey demedim!
Go on!
Devam edin!
Have at it!
Kavganızı görelim!
Roger! Oden! Don't encourage them!
Onları cesaretlendirmeyin, Roger, Oden!
Flashy treasure's waiting for me!
Gösterişli hazine beni bekliyor!
Don't push yourself, idiot!
Kendini zorlama, seni ahmak!
I'm coming, too!
Ben de geleceğim!
Captain, take me with you!
Kaptan, beni de yanınıza alın!
You're like a little monster, huh?
Küçük bir canavar gibisin, ha?
Although they bicker constantly,
Daima çekişseler dahi,
in the end, Redtaro took it upon himself to look after him.
sonunda Kızıl-taro ona bakmak için gönüllü oldu.
I cannot tell if they are close friends or bitter rivals.
Dostlar mı yoksa düşmanlar mı bilemiyorum.
Take me with you...
Beni de götürün...
While Buggyjiro is very upset over this, are are fine with this outcome, Redtaro?
Buggy-jiro karalar bağlamışken, sen hâline razı mısın gerçekten, Kızıl-taro?
Oden. Captain.
Oden-san, Kaptan.
If we wanna go there, we'll take our own ships someday!
Oraya gitmek istersek bir gün kendi gemimizle gideriz zaten!
♪ Gather up all of the crew! ♪ ♪ Time to ship out Binks' brew! ♪
♪ Binks'in sakesini ulaştırmaya gidelim ♪
♪ Pirates, we tirelessly ♪ ♪ are challenging the sea! ♪
♪ Bize derler korsan, aşarız tüm denizleri ♪
♪ With the waves to rest our heads, ♪ ♪ ships beneath us as our beds! ♪
♪ Dalgalar yastığımız gemimiz yatağımız ♪
♪ Hoisted high upon the mast ♪ ♪ our Jolly Roger flies! ♪
♪ Bayrağımızda her zaman vardır kurukafamız ♪
The Roger Pirates finally did it!
Roger Korsanları sonunda başardı!
That pirate, Roger, is the first man in history to circumnavigate the world!
Şu korsan Roger, tarihte dünyanın çevresini dolaşan ilk kişi oldu!
♪ Somewhere in the endless sky, ♪ ♪ stormy winds are blowing by! ♪
♪ Fırtına bulutları, sardı yine gökleri ♪
♪ Waves are dancing, evening comes, ♪ ♪ it's time to sound the drums! ♪
♪ Dalgalar dans eder, vurun davula çalsın müzikler ♪
Someone's finally conquered the sea!
Sonunda denizlerin hâkimi olan biri çıktı.
He's truly the king of the sea!
Harbiden denizlerin kralı oldu be!
♪ Steady men, and never fear, ♪ ♪ future skies are always clear! ♪
♪ Korku rüzgârına kapılıp da umutsuzluğa düşme ♪
The King of the Pirates!
Korsanlar Kralı!
♪ Pound your feet, clap your hands ♪ ♪ till sunny days return! ♪
♪ Yarın güneş, yeniden doğacak elbette ♪
GOLD ROGER, KING OF THE PIRATES x;2rzLBytaEUb 4KPRBJp;fH:t6 y:7pHM.MlCunS ;38FAEWz!j8aN EwqbLg7mkgMOw AqMa0eMMz1zTx
KORSANLAR KRALI, GOLD ROGER
GOLD ROGER, KING OF THE PIRATES x;2rzLBytaEUb 4KPRBJp;fH:t6 y:7pHM.MlCunS ;38FAEWz!j8aN EwqbLg7mkgMOw AqMa0eMMz1zTx
x;2rzLBytaEUb 4KPRBJp;fH:t6 y:7pHM.MlCunS
GOLD ROGER, KING OF THE PIRATES x;2rzLBytaEUb 4KPRBJp;fH:t6 y:7pHM.MlCunS ;38FAEWz!j8aN EwqbLg7mkgMOw AqMa0eMMz1zTx
;38FAEWz!j8aN EwqbLg7mkgMOw AqMa0eMMz1zTx
GOLD ROGER, KING OF THE PIRATES x;2rzLBytaEUb 4KPRBJp;fH:t6 y:7pHM.MlCunS ;38FAEWz!j8aN EwqbLg7mkgMOw AqMa0eMMz1zTx
KORSANLAR KRALI, GOLD ROGER
GOLD ROGER, KING OF THE PIRATES x;2rzLBytaEUb 4KPRBJp;fH:t6 y:7pHM.MlCunS ;38FAEWz!j8aN EwqbLg7mkgMOw AqMa0eMMz1zTx
x;2rzLBytaEUb 4KPRBJp;fH:t6 y:7pHM.MlCunS
GOLD ROGER, KING OF THE PIRATES x;2rzLBytaEUb 4KPRBJp;fH:t6 y:7pHM.MlCunS ;38FAEWz!j8aN EwqbLg7mkgMOw AqMa0eMMz1zTx
;38FAEWz!j8aN EwqbLg7mkgMOw AqMa0eMMz1zTx
GOLD ROGER, KING OF THE PIRATES x;2rzLBytaEUb 4KPRBJp;fH:t6 y:7pHM.MlCunS ;38FAEWz!j8aN EwqbLg7mkgMOw AqMa0eMMz1zTx
KORSANLAR KRALI, GOLD ROGER
GOLD ROGER, KING OF THE PIRATES x;2rzLBytaEUb 4KPRBJp;fH:t6 y:7pHM.MlCunS ;38FAEWz!j8aN EwqbLg7mkgMOw AqMa0eMMz1zTx
KORSANLAR KRALI, GOLD ROGER
GOLD ROGER, KING OF THE PIRATES x;2rzLBytaEUb 4KPRBJp;fH:t6 y:7pHM.MlCunS ;38FAEWz!j8aN EwqbLg7mkgMOw AqMa0eMMz1zTx
KORSANLAR KRALI, GOLD ROGER
GOLD ROGER, KING OF THE PIRATES x;2rzLBytaEUb 4KPRBJp;fH:t6 y:7pHM.MlCunS ;38FAEWz!j8aN EwqbLg7mkgMOw AqMa0eMMz1zTx
KORSANLAR KRALI, GOLD ROGER
GOLD ROGER, KING OF THE PIRATES x;2rzLBytaEUb 4KPRBJp;fH:t6 y:7pHM.MlCunS ;38FAEWz!j8aN EwqbLg7mkgMOw AqMa0eMMz1zTx
x;2rzLBytaEUb 4KPRBJp;fH:t6 y:7pHM.MlCunS
GOLD ROGER, KING OF THE PIRATES x;2rzLBytaEUb 4KPRBJp;fH:t6 y:7pHM.MlCunS ;38FAEWz!j8aN EwqbLg7mkgMOw AqMa0eMMz1zTx
KORSANLAR KRALI, GOLD ROGER
GOLD ROGER, KING OF THE PIRATES x;2rzLBytaEUb 4KPRBJp;fH:t6 y:7pHM.MlCunS ;38FAEWz!j8aN EwqbLg7mkgMOw AqMa0eMMz1zTx
x;2rzLBytaEUb 4KPRBJp;fH:t6 y:7pHM.MlCunS
GOLD ROGER, KING OF THE PIRATES x;2rzLBytaEUb 4KPRBJp;fH:t6 y:7pHM.MlCunS ;38FAEWz!j8aN EwqbLg7mkgMOw AqMa0eMMz1zTx
KORSANLAR KRALI, GOLD ROGER
GOLD ROGER, KING OF THE PIRATES x;2rzLBytaEUb 4KPRBJp;fH:t6 y:7pHM.MlCunS ;38FAEWz!j8aN EwqbLg7mkgMOw AqMa0eMMz1zTx
KORSANLAR KRALI, GOLD ROGER
The day we reached the final island,
Son adaya vardığımız günde,
we learned everything about the world.
dünya hakkındaki her şeyi öğrendik.
We uncovered the mysteries of the Void Century...
Kayıp Yüzyıl'ı,
the people of the D...
"D." isminin gizemini,
and the ancient weapons.
Antik silahları öğrendik.
We also learned Wano's borders were once open.
Eskiden Wano'nun sınırlarının açık olduğunu da öğrendik.
♪ As a kid, I had a dream ♪ ♪ of a dazzling treasure ♪
♪ Çocukken bir hayalim vardı, parlak bir hazine ♪
♪ I had a map in my head ♪ ♪ that I knew would lead me ♪
♪ Zihnimde saklı bir harita, götürürdü gizlice ♪
When we laid our eyes upon that extraordinary treasure...
Bu olağanüstü hazineye gözlerimizi diktiğimizde...
all Roger could do...
Roger'ın tek yapabildiği şey...
♪ Charted a course all on my own, ♪ ♪ so nobody would beat me ♪
♪ Kimse beni geçmesin diye, çizdim yolu tek başıma ♪
was laugh.
gülmek oldu.
So did we!
Biz de öyle yaptık!
♪ The promised land was in my hand ♪ ♪ drew a line in the sand ♪
♪ O vaat edilen diyarda, sınırlar çekildi usulca ♪
We laughed until tears streamed down our faces!
Gözlerimizden yaşlar gelene kadar güldük.
♪ Day after day ♪
♪ Günbegün... ♪
♪ Billowing dust is filling all my daydreams ♪
♪ Toz bulutları sarıyor tüm hayallerimi ♪
Oh, Joyboy, how I wish...
Joyboy, çok isterdim...
♪ There will come a time ♪
♪ Öyle bir zaman gelecek ki ♪
that I could have lived in the same era as you.
Keşke seninle aynı çağda yaşasaydık.
♪ Yeah, in the end ♪
♪ Ve nihayetinde... ♪
How could you leave this stupendous treasure?!
Bu muazzam hazineyi nasıl arkanda bırakabildin?!
♪  It will be nothing but a fading echo ♪
♪ Silinip giden bir yankı kalacak sadece ♪
A tale full of laughter...
Ne kadar da komik bir hikaye...
♪ But if the world ever changes ♪ ♪ I'll call out your name ♪
♪ Ama dünya bir gün değişse bile, çağırırım yine seni ♪
Hey, everyone...
Hey, millet!
We're the first people to reach this final island in 800 years. Why don't we give it a name?
Tam 800 yıl sonra bu adaya varan ilk kişileriz! Hadi bir isim koyalım şuraya!
♪ We could return to a time ♪ ♪ when our lives were still the same ♪
♪ Döneriz belki o günlere, kaybetmediğimiz her anı gibi ♪
Let's call it...
Şöyle diyelim...
♪ Take me to the place where memories remain ♪
♪ Götür beni oraya, anıların solmadığı yere ♪
♪ Please don't ever let them fade ♪
♪ Lütfen unutulmasına asla izin verme ♪
Laugh Tale!
Laugh Tale!